### JARROD WHITLEY



(817) 691-5468 me@jarrodwhitley.com

2417 Hampton Dr Little Elm TX 75068 United States

### **PROFILE**

I'm a passionate creative who is hopelessly in love with beautiful and functional design. I have ten years of work experience in various web and graphic related positions and have worn many hats ranging from UI/UX Designer to Frontend Web Developer. I love finding creative ways to overcome design and programming challenges.

I love to write stories, hike, camp, and spend time with my family. I'm a huge fan of rowdy board games, ping pong, and live music.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Web Application Engineer, Turnstyle(Lifeblue); Plano, TX Mar 2024 - Nov 2024

- Enhance and maintain the Turnstyle product using Vue3, ensuring optimal performance and seamless user experience.
- Onboarding clients by customizing their websites to meet branding and business needs, ensuring a smooth transition and positive client experience.
- Collaborating with the team to build supporting features around data management for a full-function stadium seat selection application

# Front End Developer, Highland Homes; Plano, TX July 2019 - Mar 2024

- Mockup designs for new applications using Adobe XD
- Create SPAs using Vue.js for everything from mobile devices to 50" touchscreen kiosks.
- Design, test, and implement split tests to improve website conversion rates and overall usability
- Created and maintained proprietary mobile app with NativeScript-Vue
- · Maintained legacy Wordpress sites

#### Front End Developer, Boomer Benefits; Fort Worth, TX — Jun 2018 - Jul 2019

- Update and maintain all company Wordpress sites
- Create custom webapps with Javascript

- Manage and improve site security through vetting of plugins and setting up htaccess restrictions
- Design responsive email marketing campaigns

## Front End Developer & UI/UX Designer, PC Game Match; Fort Worth, TX Dec 2017 - Jun 2018

- Designed UI/UX for application
- Wrote all front-end code for application

# Sr. Website Consultant, Thryv; Grapevine, TX May 2016 - Dec 2017

- Consult with clients and gather information necessary for building a
  website that meets and exceeds their needs
- Communicate client needs to web design team and oversee website development
- · Write SEO content for website
- Modify current client's websites
- · Write custom code for client websites
- Create graphic assets for websites

# Web Developer & UI/UX Designer; MJBI Feb 2014 - Jan 2016

- Management and maintenance of Wordpress sites
- · Mockup designs for web/print applications
- · Creating web/print graphics
- · Creating monthly and special event emailers
- · Managing email campaigns
- Creating marketing strategies for gaining new donors

#### **EDUCATION**

East Central High School — Graduate, 2003

#### **SKILLS**

- Vue
- React
- Javascript

- UI/UX Design
- CSS3 / SCSS
- Bootstrap/Foundation/Tailwind
- · NativeScript-vue
- Git
- Responsive design
- Split testing
- Adobe XD
- Adobe Photoshop
- I am a self-starter and I excel at learning new things quickly

### **PROFESSIONAL REFERENCES**

Tyler Walker, Sr. Web Application Engineer, Turnstyle(Lifeblue) <a href="mailto:tyler@lifeblue.com">tyler@lifeblue.com</a>

Jean Wallace, VP of Product, Turnstyle(Lifeblue) <a href="mailto:jean@lifeblue.com">jean@lifeblue.com</a>

#### **PERSONAL REFERENCES**

Dewayne Holden +417 861 2537

Michael Bleecker

+ 972 415 4000